backpackit.com 2006-12-06

# 

### BACKPACK PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of [Terms of Service](http://www.backpackit.com/terms.html), or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if 37signals or Backpack is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, 37signals will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

INFORMATION GATHERING AND USAGE  

  * When you register for Backpack we ask for information such as your name, email address, billing address, credit card information. **Members who sign up for the free account are not required to enter a credit card.**
  * 37signals uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

COOKIES  

  * A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.
  * Cookies are required to use the Backpack service.
  * We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to log-in to your Backpack Project Site after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

DATA STORAGE  
37signals uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Backpack. Although 37signals owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Basecamp application, you retain all rights to your data. 

INFORMATION RIGHTS AND PUBLICITY  
Unless you notify 37signals otherwise in writing, You hereby grant to 37signals and its wholly owned subsidiaries a limited license to use Your trade names, trademarks, service marks, logos, domain names and other distinctive brand features ("Brand Features") in presentations, marketing materials, web sites, customer lists, and financial reports.

DISCLOSURE  

  * 37signals may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the [Terms of Service](http://www.backpackit.com/terms.html).

CHANGES  
37signals may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Backpack primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

QUESTIONS  
Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to support at 37signals.com or by mail at: 37signals, 400 North May Street #301, Chicago, IL 60622 USA 

Copyright 2003-2005 37signals LLC. All rights reserved.
